Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series IV: Governor
  - Sub-series A: 1978 Campaign
    - Correspondence –Outgoing –Post Election, By County
      - Franklin County (Box 80, Folder 42)
      - Gibson County (Box 80, Folder 43)
      - Giles County (Box 80, Folder 44)
      - Grainger County (Box 80, Folder 45)
      - Greene County (Box 80, Folder 46)
      - Grundy County (Box 80, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence –Outgoing –Post Election, By County
      - Hamblen County (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Hamilton County (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Hancock County (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Hardeman County (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Hardin County (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Hawkins County (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Haywood County (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Henderson County (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Henry County (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Hickman County (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Houston County (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Humphreys County (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Jackson County (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Jefferson County (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Johnson County (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - Knox County (1 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - Knox County (2 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Knox County (3 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - Lake County (Box 81, Folder 19)
      - Lauderdale County (Box 81, Folder 20)
      - Lawrence County (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - Lincoln County (Box 81, Folder 22)
      - Loudon County (Box 81, Folder 23)
      - McMinn County (Box 81, Folder 24)
      - McNairy County (Box 81, Folder 25)
      - Macon County (Box 81, Folder 26)
      - Madison County (Box 81, Folder 27)
      - Marion County (Box 81, Folder 28)
      - Marshall County (Box 81, Folder 29)
      - Maury County (Box 81, Folder 30)
      - Monroe County (Box 81, Folder 31)
      - Montgomery County (Box 81, Folder 32)
      - Morgan County (Box 81, Folder 33)
      - Obion County (Box 81, Folder 34)
      - Overton County (Box 81, Folder 35)
      - Polk County (Box 81, Folder 36)
      - Putnam County (Box 81, Folder 37)
      - Rhea County (Box 81, Folder 38)
      - Roane County (Box 81, Folder 39)
      - Robertson County (Box 81, Folder 40)
      - Rutherford County (Box 81, Folder 41)
      - Scott County (Box 81, Folder 42)
      - Sequatchie County (Box 81, Folder 43)
      - Sevier County (Box 81, Folder 44)
      - Shelby County (1 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 45)
      - Shelby County (2 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 46)
      - Shelby County (3 of 3) (Box 81, Folder 47)
      - Smith County (Box 81, Folder 48)
      - Stewart County (Box 81, Folder 49)
      - Sullivan County (Box 81, Folder 50)
      - Sumner County (Box 81, Folder 51)
      - Tipton County (Box 81, Folder 52)
      - Unicoi County (Box 81, Folder 53)
      - Union County (Box 81, Folder 54)
      - Warren County (Box 81, Folder 55)
      - Washington County (Box 81, Folder 56)
      - Wayne County (Box 81, Folder 57)
      - Weakley County (Box 81, Folder 58)
      - White County (Box 81, Folder 59)
      - Williamson County (Box 81, Folder 60)
      - Wilson County (Box 81, Folder 61)
      - Out-Of-State (Box 81, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence –Outgoing –Post Election –Ted Welch, Chronological
      - November 21, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - November 22, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - November 27, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - November 28, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - November 29, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - November 30, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - November 30, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - December 1, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - December 4, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - December 5, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - December 6, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - December 6, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - December 7, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - December 8, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - December 9, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - December 11, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - December 12, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - December 13, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - December 14, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - December 15, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 20)
      - December 18, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - December 18, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - December 19, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - December 20, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - December 21, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence –Incoming –Post Election, Alphabetical
      - A-Anderson (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Annis-Ayers (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - B-Bawsom (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Beach-Bewley (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Bibb-Blick (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Bobbitt-Boyd (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - Bradley-Britten (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Brock - Broyles (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Brunson-Byrge (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - C-Caudill (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Chance-Clinton (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - Coble-Cox (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - Craig-Cutshaw (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - D-DeWitt (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - Dice-Dyer (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - E-Ewers (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - F-Fishman (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - Flanigan-Fulton (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence –Incoming –Post Election, Alphabetical
      - G-Gower (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Graham-Gurkin (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - H-Hanover (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Haralson-Haywood (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Heard-Hewgley (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Hickman-Hutchison (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - I-Inman (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - J-Justice (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - K-Ketchey (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - Khan-Kitts (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Kline-Kuykendall (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - L-Lawson (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Lear-Lyle (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - Mc-McReynolds (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - M-Mayfield (Box 84, Folder 15)
      - Meadows-Mitchum (Box 84, Folder 16)
      - Mobbs-Myint (Box 84, Folder 17)
      - N-Norwood (Box 84, Folder 18)
      - O-Owen (Box 84, Folder 19)
      - P-Payne (Box 84, Folder 20)
      - Pedritti-Plunket (Box 84, Folder 21)
      - Polis-Putman (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence –Incoming –Post Election, Alphabetical
      - Q-Quinn (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - R-Rentschler (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Ricketts-Rogers (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Romero-Barceló-Ruggles (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - S-Scruggs (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Seigenthaler-Shrum (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Sickle-Siskin (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Slaughter-Springer (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Stapp-Swafford (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - T-Thornton (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - Timms-Tyree (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - V-Via (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - W-Watson (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Wead-Whittle (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - Wilder-Wright (Box 85, Folder 15)
      - Y-Yount (Box 85, Folder 16)
      - Z-Zerfoss (Box 85, Folder 17)
      - Unidentified (Box 85, Folder 18)
      - Englewood Elementary School (Box 85, Folder 19)
      - McEwen School (Box 85, Folder 20)
      - Pope School (Box 85, Folder 21)
      - Tennessee School for the Deaf (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Schedules for Lamar Alexander
      - Lamar Alexander, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Lamar Alexander –Kick Off (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Lamar Alexander –Airplane Schedules (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Lamar Alexander, January 1978 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Lamar Alexander, February 1-13, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Lamar Alexander, February 14-28, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Lamar Alexander, March 1-14, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Lamar Alexander, March 15-31, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Lamar alexander, April 1-16, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - Lamar Alexander, April 17-30, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Lamar Alexander, May 1-15, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Lamar Alexander, May 16-31, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - Lamar Alexander, June 1-17, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Lamar Alexander, June 17-30, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - Lamar Alexander, July 1-16, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 15)
      - Lamar Alexander, July 17-31, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 16)
      - Lamar Alexander, August 1-15, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - Lamar Alexander, August 16-31, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 18)
      - Lamar Alexander, September 1-15, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 19)
      - Lamar Alexander, September 16-30, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Schedules for Lamar Alexander
    - Schedules for Honey Alexander
      - Lamar Alexander, October 1-15, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Lamar Alexander, October 16-31, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Lamar Alexander, November 1978 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Lamar Alexander, December 1978 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Tom Ingram Copies, January 1978 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Tom Ingram Copies, February 1978 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Tom Ingram Copies, March 1978 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Tom Ingram Copies, April 1978 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Flexible Schedules (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Requests for Appearances by Lamar Alexander (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - Honey Alexander (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Honey Alexander, January 1978 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Honey Alexander, February 1978 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Honey Alexander, March 1978 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - Honey Alexander, April 1978 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Honey Alexander, May 1978 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - Honey Alexander, June 1978 (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Honey Alexander, July 1978 (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Honey Alexander, August 1978 (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - Honey Alexander, September 1978 (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - Honey Alexander, October 1978 (Box 87, Folder 21)
      - Honey Alexander, November 1978 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Walk Across Tennessee
      - Proposed Route for the Walk Across Tennessee (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Chairman of the Walk Handbook (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - County Maps (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - List of People to Be Sent Newsletters (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - News From the Walk, January 1978 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - News From the Walk, February 1978 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - News From the Walk, March 1978 (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - News From the Walk, March 1978 (2 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - News From the Walk, April 1978 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      - News From the Walk, May 1978 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      - News From the Walk, June 1978 (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - News From the Walk, July 1978 (1 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - News From the Walk, July 1978 (2 of 2) (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - News From the Walk, August 1978 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Walk Across Tennessee
      - News From the Walk, September 1978 (1 of 4) (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - News From the Walk, September 1978 (2 of 4) (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - News From the Walk, September 1978 (3 of 4) (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - News From the Walk, September 1978 (4 of 4) (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - News From the Walk, October 1978 (1 of 5) (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - News From the Walk, October 1978 (2 of 5) (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - News From the Walk, October 1978 (3 of 5) (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - News From the Walk, October 1978 (4 of 5) (Box 89, Folder 8)
      - News From the Walk, October 1978 (5 of 5) (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - News From the Walk, November 1978 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - News From the Walk, Undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - Article on Lamar Alexander in “Nashville”, May 1978 (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Advertisement in “U.S. News & World Report”, February 6, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Walk Across Tennessee
      - Kick Off Newspaper Clippings (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Kick Off Newspaper Clippings –Photocopies (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Newspaper Clippings, January 1978 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper Clippings, February 1978 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Newspaper Clippings, March 1-17, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Newspaper Clippings, March 22-31, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Newspaper Clippings, April 5-6, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Newspaper Clippings, April 7-19, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Newspaper Clippings, April 22-28, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Newspaper Clippings, May 4-5, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Newspaper Clippings, May21, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Newspaper Clippings, May 26, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - Newspaper Clippings, June 1978 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      - Newspaper Clippings, July 1978 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - Newspaper Clippings, August 1978 (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Newspaper Clippings, September 1978 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Newspaper Clippings, October 1978 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Special Media (Box 90, Folder 18)
      - Mailing Addresses for News Clippings (Box 90, Folder 19)
      - Research Paper “Lamar Alexander’s Cross-State Campaign Walk” by Carole Klein, August 15, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Walk Across Tennessee
      - Zip Code Research (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Post Office Listings (1 of 2) (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Post Office Listings (2 of 2) (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Lodging and Support (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Lodging, January 25-April 13, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Lodging, April 14-May31, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Lodging, June1-July 8, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Lodging, July 9-August 14, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Lodging, August 15-31, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Lodging, September1-30, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Lodging, October 1-30, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Lodging, November 1978 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Thank You Letters, January 1978 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Thank You Letters, February 1-3, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - Thank You Letters, February 6-16, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 15)
      - Thank You Letters, February 17-28, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 16)
      - Thank You Letters, March 2-15, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Walk Across Tennessee
      - Thank You Letters, March 16-31, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Thank You Letters, April 1-17, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Thank You Letters, April 20-26, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Thank You Letters, May 1-10, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Thank You Letters, May 11, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Thank You Letters, May 12-25, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Thank You Letters, June 1-9, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Thank You Letters, June12-29, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Thank You Letters, July 3-11, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Thank You Letters, July 19-31, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Thank You Letters, August 1978 (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Thank You Letters, September 1-3, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Thank You Letters, September 8-23, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - Thank You Letters, October 2-15, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 14)
      - Thank You Letters, October 15-30, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 15)
      - List of People Lamar Alexander Stayed with During Walk (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Keel Hunt Files
      - Miscellaneous (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Position Statements (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Requests for Position Statements, January-February1978 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Requests for Position Statements, March 1978 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Requests for Position Statements, April 1978 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Requests for Position Statements, May 1978 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Requests for Position Statements, June 2-13, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Requests for Position Statements, June 15-29, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Requests for Position Statements, July 5-19, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Requests for Position Statements, July 21-31, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - Requests for Position Statements, August 1-10, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Requests for Position Statements, August 14-31, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Requests for Position Statements, September 1-6, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Requests for Position Statements, September 7-13, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - Requests for Position Statements, September 15-29, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Requests for Position Statements, October 2-5, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - Requests for Position Statements, October 6-9, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 17)
      - Requests for Position Statements, October 10-13, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 18)
      - Requests for Position Statements, October 16-18, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 19)
      - Requests for Position Statements, October 19-20, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 20)
      - Requests for Position Statements, October 23-30, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 21)
      - Requests for Position Statements, November 1-3, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 22)
      - Requests for Position Statements, November 6, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 23)
      - Requests for Position Statements, November 6-10, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Tom Ingram Files
      - 1977 Calendar (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - 1978 Calendar (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Bailey, Deardourff & Associates, Inc. –Goal Setting, 1978-1979 (1 of 2) (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Bailey, Deardourff & Associates, Inc. –Goal Setting, 1978-1979 (2 of 2) (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Bass, Berry & Sims (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Files (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Drafts of Letters and Speeches (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Fundraising Goals (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Lamar Alexander –1977 Income Tax and Financial Statements (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Media Services (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Ray Blanton Research (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Jake Butcher Research (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Bob Clement Research (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Memos and Letters (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - Notes (1 of 35) (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - Notes (2 of 35) (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - Notes (3 of 35) (Box 94, Folder 17)
      - Notes (4 of 35) (Box 94, Folder 18)
      - Notes (5 of 35) (Box 94, Folder 19)
      - Notes (6 of 35) (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Tom Ingram Files
      - Notes (7 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Notes (8 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Notes (9 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Notes (10 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Notes (11 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Notes (12 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Notes (13 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Notes (14 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Notes (15 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Notes (16 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Notes (17 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Notes (18 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Notes (19 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Notes (20 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Notes (21 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Notes (22 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - Notes (23 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - Notes (24 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Notes (25 of 35) (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Tom Ingram Files
      - Notes (26 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Notes (27 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Notes (28 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Notes (29 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Notes (30 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Notes (31 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Notes (32 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Notes (33 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Notes (34 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Notes (35 of 35) (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - November Voting Poll (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Polls (1 of 3) (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Polls (2 of 3) (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Polls (3 of 3) (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - Polls –Political Opinion in Tennessee’s First Congressional District (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - Republican National Committee –Correspondence, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - Ruby Tuesday Financial Statement (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - Tennessee Gubernatorial Election Survey, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - Post-Election Notes (1 of 3) (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - Post-Election Notes (2 of 3) (Box 96, Folder 20)
      - Post-Election Notes (3 of 3) (Box 96, Folder 21)
      - Post-Election Congratulations (1 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 22)
      - Post-Election Congratulations (2 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 23)
      - Governor-Elect –Correspondence (Box 96, Folder 24)
      - Inauguration (Box 96, Folder 25)
      - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 96, Folder 26)
      - Notes (Box 96, Folder 27)
      - Transition (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - Finance
    - Susan Simons Files
      - Correspondence (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - County Finance Chairmen Lists (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Anderson County-Bledsoe County (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Blount County (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Bradley County (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Campbell County-Claiborne County (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Cocke County-Cumberland County (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Decatur County-Grundy County (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Hamblen County-Hamilton County (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Hardeman County-Humphreys County (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Jackson County-Knox County (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Lake County-Loudon County (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Macon County-Morgan County (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Obion County-Rutherford County (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Scott County-Sumner County (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - County Finance Chairmen –Correspondence –Tipton County-Wilson County (Box 97, Folder 16)
      - County Totals (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Finance
    - Susan Simons Files
      - First Disclosure (1 of 2) (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - First Disclosure (2 of 2) (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Second Disclosure (1 of 2) (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Second Disclosure (2 of 2) (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Third Disclosure (1 of 3) (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Third Disclosure (2 of 3) (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Third Disclosure (3 of 3) (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Fourth Disclosure (1 of 3) (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Fourth Disclosure (2 of 3) (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Fourth Disclosure (3 of 3) (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Fifth Disclosure (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Sixth Disclosure (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Finance
    - Susan Simons Files
      - Early Planning (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Events (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - First Tennessee Bank –Account Ledger (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Fundraising Plans (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - List of Contributors, Undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Out-of-State Finance (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, February 8, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, March 9, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, March 9, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, May 10, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, July 10, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, July 26, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Finance
    - Susan Simons Files
    - General Finance Files
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, July 26, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, September 1, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, October 30, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, October 30, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Reports of Receipts and Expenditures, December 7, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Requests to See Campaign Disclosure Forms (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Shelby County (1 of 2) (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Shelby County (2 of 2) (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Account Ledger (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Account Ledger –A-D (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Account Ledger –E-I (Box 100, Folder 11)